Tristan Saragosa



I want to work for a company that has the potential for growth and will allow me to learn and grow with them. I have some experience in computer science as well as accounting. I am currently pursuing my bachelors degree and working towards obtaining my real estate license.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Busser/Food Runner/Barback/Server/Bartender

JW Marriott Camelback Inn - Paradise Valley, AZ April 2021 to Present

I am responsible for cleaning and setting tables when I am bussing as well as maintaining the outside patio. When food running I am responsible for helping run food to customers tables. As a barback I am responsible for setting up and closing the bar as well as helping the bartender make and serve drinks. Serving makes me responsible for greeting my tables and taking there orders to make sure they have a great experience. When I am the bartender I am responsible for making drinks and serving people at the bar as well managing the bar and opening and closing the bar. I will also work private events.

Team Member

Target - Scottsdale, AZ October 2019 to March 2020

I was a team member at target and worked in the electronics section. I already had customer service experience from working in a restaurant but I was able to have more one on one service experiences. I learned a lot about understanding issues the guest was having and ways to walk them through the solution.

Busser

Oregano's Pizza Bistro - Flagstaff, AZ March 2017 to August 2017

I was responsible for keeping all the tables ready for guests. I had to work as a team with other bussers, hosts, and servers to make sure tables were clean as well as keeping up on emptying trash and filling ice.

Host

Oregano's Pizza Bistro - Paradise Valley, AZ March 2015 to August 2015

I was responsible for seating guests in a timely manner. I had to work with bussers and servers to make sure tables were clean and that servers were not over sat. I learned a lot about customer service during my time at this job.

Education

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Scottsdale Community College - Paradise Valley, AZ March 2018 to Present

High school diploma or GED in N/A

Horizon High School - Scottsdale, AZ August 2011 to March 2015

Skills

- Busser
- Java
- Computer Science
- JavaScript
- Restaurant Experience
- Swift
- HTML5
- Customer Service
- Computer Skills
- Cash Handling
- Computer Literacy
- OOP
- C/C++
- CSS